Okay, I clicked on the wrong button.
>> We are live.
>> And we are live. Yes, we're live because
we can. Uh, tap Mitchell.
>> Yes. How are you?
>> I'm doing good. Uh, productive day. I'm
I'm I'm feeling good about my newish
workflows of work. It's cool.
>> Happy that they reset the timers on
cloud code yesterday.
>> Yeah, I I I saw that today, but I was
already full and Yeah. Oh, that's why I
have some reserve uh h
>> yesterday. I think yesterday evening
they reseted it again.
>> Nice. Oh, yeah. Because there is a bug,
right? There was there was a bug. Okay,
that's cool. I like I like though
honestly I like them. I I like I like
did a lot.
>> Well, I think they actually did a lot.
They multiplied the amount that you can
use. They did a second reset in within
30 days.
>> Thanks to thanks to Elon Musk for
providing usage, I guess.
>> Yes, they actually have spare spare CPU.
>> Yeah. Do you think they're gonna get
right off those limits one day?
Uh, I think they just want I maybe it's
wrong, but I think it's like drugs. They
get everybody addicted and when nobody
can do without, they just up the price.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Okay, that's going to be
another live stream. We're gonna red
alert. You don't have subscription
anymore. It's all API usage. We're gonna
we're gonna we're gonna
>> I know this was not on on the list, but
Copilot did it right. They swapped the
entire AI uh copilot usage to API keys.
>> Do you know anyone who use copilot
anywhere?
>> Yeah, schools.
>> Oh,
>> so schools have the entire Microsoft
setup because they get discounts uh from
Microsoft and they encourage all the
students to use Microsoft Copilot on the
IT education.
>> Jesus.
>> So Dale SWAT I don't even know. I I need
to ask my uh
>> my interns what they are doing
>> like I I don't even think I you I tried
copilot AI
for me it it isn't it just codeex
>> yeah I mean
>> codeex is from Microsoft
GitHub is from Microsoft GitHub copilot
is like codeex so why don't just use
codeex
>> wait What? What? Codex? What? What is
OpenAI?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Microsoft is what what are
they using? Microsoft is is a
shareholder in
>> shareholder of Open AI but um uh that's
why also they use entropics and then
they stopped the licensing like uh last
week or two weeks ago.
>> Yeah. They don't want to give away the
secrets to uh entropic.
>> Exactly.
>> So yeah. and and they want to push like
copilot usage blah blah blah to internal
Microsoft but
>> yeah just for everybody who is thinking
about buying copilot don't do it so bad
>> yeah it's it's like using mro in France
but that's
>> it's one of the only subscriptions where
you cannot do a monthly but you have to
buy a whole year
>> that should make you think because
that's not that's not encouraging
>> yeah doing a yearly subscription in AI
It's like
>> Yeah, it's like a big bet.
>> Yeah. And we're not doing it. Maybe
maybe we should uh move to Y on
anthropic and codex though because we
basically need both.
>> Yeah, we use them all the time.
>> True, true, true, true. But yeah, for
today, let's talk about Yupus Yupus
4.8.
>> Yes, it dropped last week.
>> Yes, sir. Uh, okay. Okay, I'm I'm going
to do the introduction and uh and uh and
let's go. Perfect.
>> Okay.
Opus 4.8 dropped last week. We are using
every day like we are addicted to it and
it's kind of fun to play with it. Uh
uh but is it is it the uh best model
ever created? We are going to check that
in this video right now. Subscribe, like
the video, and share it to your friend
because they need to watch us because we
>> Let's go. Okay, that's going to be a
quick introduction.
>> Um, cool. Uh, so yeah, what did you do
with like Opus 4.8 since last week use
case?
>> I I actually at first I compared it. So
I gave uh my prompt to Codeex and I gave
my prompt to Opus 4.8 date because I was
fully out of Opus
>> and my first issue was that's how long I
haven't been using it. I was checking
and I didn't have the 4.8.
So I had issues last time with 4.7
and I disabled automatic updates and I
was still on the old version with only
4.6. Oh,
>> so I updated first then I compared and
eventually my decision was to let codeex
uh do all the programming development
coding everything
and have Opus 4.8
on max effort do the entire security
check uh coding check searching for bugs
testing and then give a reply to codeex
to make the improvements.
>> Okay. Do you still plan your issues like
your task?
>> Uh, yes, all the time.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay.
>> I think I had over 1,500 lines of um
text on my last plan.
>> Do you use Whisper Flow for planning for
writing your plans?
>> Yeah. Well, I didn't write the all. I
use Whisper Flow for inserting all my
text into Codeex and asking Codex to
write it into a full plan.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that makes sense. Yeah. And
I actually read it.
>> You read the plans?
>> Yeah. Why make a plan if you don't read
the plan?
>> Do you have a summarize card or like
something and then you go to details or
you read like the
>> I read the whole MD file because I still
plan and not a HTML.
>> Can you change the format? Oh yeah.
>> Uh do you change the format of the plan
or do you get like the is that readable?
Because sometime it's a lot of like
lines and blah blah blah. So do you
reduce or did you use caveman to plan
for example instead of like using like
long sentences you do like shorter
words?
>> Oh no it just it made it perfect. I
could read it easily. So I don't use
caveman or anything.
>> I use caveman. I use art. I use all of
them.
>> Yeah. It's like you're wrong. Fix it.
>> Yeah. Exactly.
Uh yeah and same thing like for me what
I've done I I quite okay so I tested it
because I had reserved uh usage for 4.8
>> it took me a while to switch for 4 4.6
to to 4.7 too because it was more
expensive then I start to use it and I
didn't see my usage going down. So maybe
every time they push a new model um
there is some bugs initially and like
the usage going nuts and I don't want to
lose my weekly usage in one afternoon.
So I just like uh go slow with that. So
that's why I didn't make the jump for
4.6 for 4.7 but 4.8 what did I do with
it? I was just like coding and more
front end stuff. Um, and my usage didn't
move. And honestly, that almost the
matrix
uh I want to keep. If the usage is not
going down and I just cut it like for
six hours, I like the model.
If if the model is cheap, I need to use
Yeah, I didn't even have need for it
anymore. But for like a composer uh 2.5,
I need to test it.
>> Yeah. Yeah, for sure.
>> But um Yeah.
How fast did you go through all your
tokens? How fast were you on your daily
and weekly limit?
>> Uh but because of the resets, like I
don't even know, but I'm still spending
like five uh the full uh 5,000 a month
uh
uh allocation on the your 200 uh
subscription.
>> Okay, that's good. So
on uh
today,
so for the last 30 days, okay, that's
that's wrong because that's that's not
the case. Uh it say like $300, but uh
today as on Codex as I burn $170 million
tokens.
>> Mhm.
>> Um
>> that's a lot.
>> And yeah. Okay. So on code on the codeex
bar uh it's telling me that I've burned
6,300
uh aka 10 billion token for the last 30
days. I think there is a bug on the
forex. It's probably like just uh
started to count um
not the last 30 days but just yeah it
counted just June and uh but basically
I'm burning the pro the cost of my
subscription in one day.
>> Yeah. So
>> that that's like a 30 eggs on on what
you save in money.
>> Yeah. Exactly. And uh yeah, I have a
weekly reserve like so we're gonna do a
demo after like in minutes
>> I was 4.8 and I have a reserve of like
50% in reserve. So what I usually do is
um I'm cutting in high and fast mode. So
I burn token but going way faster and
honestly like the the experience with
that it's kind of lit. I like
>> I never tried fast mode
>> but
>> I'm like
>> yeah but yeah but if you track it with
codeex and you with a codeex bar and you
have the um the reset coming soon like
if and you still have some reserve
subscription just codex fast.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Just maximize your usage.
>> Okay.
>> So then you can burn token and let's go
>> and you can go for the next restart.
Yeah that makes sense. Yeah. Um, okay.
So, when they uh announce it from the
Twitter tech,
uh, is it?
Why is it not the same site?
Another one left.
Oh, alignment. Nice. Want to keep it
that way. Boom. Was branding here.
Okay. So, the only thing that everyone
want to know is that are the numbers
bigger or not? And they are. So,
>> is it better and is it smarter?
>> Exactly. Uh, introducing code Opus 4.8.
It build it builds on Opus 4.7 with
sharper judgment, more honest honesty
about its own progress.
Yeah, that's so weird to say.
>> So that means what happened with 4.6 and
4.7?
>> Yeah, it it means like, okay, I'm done
with the task. You check, you're not
done, bro.
>> Yeah. And now I have an update. I'm not
going to lie anymore.
>> Yeah, exactly. And you're going to see
like the 4.9 will be ah, you know, we
even more honest.
>> It could have been better.
Uh because that's that's both what we
found so far, right? Like that's the
problem with Opus. It say it's done, but
it's not done.
>> Yes.
>> Uh
yes.
>> Oh, do do you hear some Oh, [__] My mic
is
>> okay.
>> Okay. Better.
>> Yes. Much better.
>> Okay. Nice. Oh, I hope before it was not
that's uh
is it okay? Good.
>> Yeah, we don't hear anything now.
>> Uh so uh the ability to work
independently for longer uh than its
predecessor available today. Same price
at the same price at 4.7. Uh okay. So
Aentic coding uh 69.2 2
uh plus 5
5 and 4.7 and 5.5 is only at 58. Um
yeah.
>> Yeah. But I still had the experience
that 5.5 was sometimes better than 4.7.
>> Yeah. But because you don't do like a
lot of agentic coding aka like you have
multiple agents doing like do you?
>> Yeah. Sometimes not all the time. So
maybe that's the difference.
>> Yeah. Almost like aentic coding is like
almost using LMS to code and you talk to
one CEO and then it's
allocate the task to a CTO front end and
blah blah blah blah blah blah.
>> It deploys the entire team.
>> Yeah.
Uh I would need to double check what I
just said because I'm not sure 100% but
uh I that's what I understood. Uh agency
terminal coding uh terminal bench. Okay.
That's the That's you talking coding the
terminal.
>> Uh 74. No, it's even like the tools the
agent using the tools on the terminal to
access a file etc.
>> 74 against 66 and 78 for 5 5.5 and
that's what we do. We are doing like
agenting terminal coding more than the
aenting coding I would say. Um multi
disciplinary reasoning 4 uh 49 57. Yeah.
Uh humanity last exam. Yeah. Okay. It's
more like uh yeah the same stuff. Uh
agotic computer use. It's like the the
agent who can use your computer. So 83
against 78 for 5.5.
Uh knowledge work GDP. Okay. GDP val.
It's like the benchmark about all of the
white collar jobs.
>> Mhm.
>> 18
1890 against uh 1769 for 5.5. So yeah,
that's that's crazy jumps. And financial
analysis 53.9
against 51. So basically don't trust it
for your taxes. But
>> yeah, taxes are still hard. See?
>> Yeah. But like if you do if you build an
app to do your financial task then you
use aentic terminal to then you know
>> Yeah. So does that I Yeah. I wouldn't
trust it then.
>> Yeah. I mean the code Yes. Because then
you build like railway to do your taxes.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But your entire planning is
on the lowest one. That's not good.
>> Uh fast model fast mode is available for
opus 4.8 eight same model roughly 2.5
the speed
uh and three times cheaper than before.
Yeah, because I think it was 2.5 the
speed but three times more expensive
than
uh 4.7
like no fast 2 fast mode is 2.5 the
speed but three times more expensive
that normal mode like
>> but what does it do? actually gives you
priority in the line when you're waiting
for an answer or
>> yeah like it's the time of like
computing before you get like the answer
it just like go way faster
>> so yeah I guess I I don't know how it's
it's working in the back end but they
probably have like some yeah priority
request or something
or more compute even uh makes uh in
cloud code op makes call like an
experiment experience engineer without
needing constant checking Ah, that's not
true.
>> Um, it's down track across long running
session and follow walk through in your
repo so you can end off a feature or bug
sweep while you focus on what's next.
Yeah, know you're right. Uh, yeah,
still still a lot to check after that,
right? And finally, one of the biggest
promising that uh even like more agentic
world uh dynamic workflows for the
hardest task make a plan run hundreds of
parallel sub agent aka like you don't
have a weekly subscription anymore like
that's it's done
>> and verifies it works before reporting
back think immigration touching hundreds
of files.
>> Yeah. This is like the ultra effort.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Is it? No.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It It does. It is the extra
high but in parallel mode.
>> Oh, okay.
>> You can check it in the terminal. It
will show what it does.
>> Uh introducing dynamics workflow. H
we're introducing dynamic workflow
include code helping take the most
challenging task end to end. Okay.
What would normally plan in quarters? No
finishing days. Let's go.
>> So from 90 days to three days.
>> Yeah, we uh we we can code Slack end to
end in a couple of days.
>> Yeah.
>> Pay inventory. Yeah, that looks like a I
didn't try it. Did Did you? Yeah. Ultra
code.
>> I tried it. Yes.
>> Ask CL to create a dynamic workflow
directly or switch on a new code
specific settings called ultra code.
This is accessed through the effort menu
and it set up the effort level to XI
while letting CL decide automatically
when to use workflow to handle your
task. Okay, nice. Okay. Uh we can we can
use that. Uh we're going to use my
subscription to for that for a little
demo. Uh okay, so rewrite B dynamic
workflow. Oh, they they rewrote bun, you
know, the npm package manager
>> the yeah uh alternative uh to rust.
>> So they use that. Oh, interesting.
>> Oh, that's cool.
>> Yeah.
Or it works with when a workflow kicks
off cloud plan dynamically based on your
prompt wreck it into subtask and fans
the work out across sub agent. Okay.
Okay.
>> Yeah. So it it is planning itself.
Okay. So, you give the prompt and then
it's Okay. Okay. Okay. We're gonna We're
gonna try that now. Gonna be fun. Uh,
okay. So, I think that's it. We
basically saw like the biggest stuff.
Yeah. Capability, whatever. Whatever. La
brunching today. Dynamic workflow,
effort control, messages, API. I think
that's it. Okay. Uh, yeah. benchmark for
the the new uh alling grill like no the
new the new
the new benchmark that everyone likes.
>> Yes, I'm going to put that in dark mode.
That would be easier. Um so 4.8 high is
uh what is it? Average cost per task.
Okay, so it's cheaper than uh GPT 5.4.
Where is 5.5?
Oh, it's here. Okay. Okay. So, 5.5 is
more expensive than 4.8. Yeah, but it's
XI. Where is the Okay. No.
Where is the extra? Oh, the max. Okay.
So, 58 plus minus. So, 12. Yeah. Okay.
That's
>> Yeah. And they only added GPT 5.4x high.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Oh no. Oh 5.5x high as well.
>> So 5
4.8 is high but x high is here but the
score is less. Okay. But there is no I'm
not crazy. Right.
>> No I don't see it.
>> Uh AQ. Okay. So GPT 4.8 4.4. I don't
care about that. I don't care about
that. Don't care about that. Yeah. Okay.
I'm not crazy. back puff puff puff.
Okay, so cheaper. Yeah. Okay, that's
kind of cool because Yeah. Okay. But
it's not the same. Is it medium? Okay,
it's medium.
>> Wait, I don't like
>> or maybe they have five medium also in
the table below because I think they
made a mistake.
>> Yeah. Uh
>> see here.
>> Yeah. So maybe they wrote it down wrong.
Yeah, medium is already
>> because the the results match
>> and yeah, it's not
so
max and here it's high
and 5.5 is default. Okay. So maybe the
table doesn't match the graph.
>> Yeah, it doesn't match. But okay, so Max
and Xi are the same, right?
>> Mhm.
>> So OPU is more expensive
and it's less than 5.5.
Okay. So all effort levels. Okay.
Ah nice. Okay. So now you write all
benchmark on SWA deep and SWA
5.5 still winning. Yes.
>> Okay. And it's way more expensive.
Xi Xi.
Okay. Same price but 12 points less.
And it's take more time too. Okay. So,
Opus 4. Is [__] Bye. Subscribe to the
channel.
>> Yeah. But still on on checking and and
doing feedback, I had some really good
results.
>> Yeah.
And what about the ultra mode stuff? Did
you
>> Yeah, that was even better because I I
tried it different times. I just had it
do feedback
uh on normal high and then I cleared the
entire history and I had to done the
exact same prompt for feedback again on
ultra mode
>> and ultra mode found a lot more.
>> Okay. Interesting.
>> And it give better explanation.
>> Okay. Okay. So, it's worth it to spend
more tokens on the highest mode. Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> Very nice. Same thing like uh you know I
like couple of weeks ago I started like
to use the low model stuff
>> and instead of switching like the low
model ef the low effort and instead of
switching model I just uh switch the
effort and it's kind of like
interesting. It's it give like good
result. So you still use the most
optimized model but on low effort and
that's enough for like renaming file or
something but sometimes with a better
sinking uh you get more file cover and
less files left over.
So yeah orchestration is like still
something that's gonna stay.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You always need to do that.
>> Yeah. So okay so following deep SWE 5.5
still have the lead. We will see how it
evolves with like 5.6 5.6 will be
interesting to to see.
>> I just hope that they make good
improvements and don't just see on hey
they brought out Opus 4.8 let's push it
already even with lesser results.
>> Yeah
>> I just hope they make it even better a
lot better. We could um we could see
some uh improvement because of the
compute too, right?
>> Mhm.
>> If they have more comput and looks like
Saman was right like if you bet on more
computing and if you buy all of the CPU
possible on earth then you will have a
better model.
>> Yeah. Because the other ones cannot use
the CPU anymore.
>> Yeah.
>> So yeah, that's going to be interesting
to to track. Uh okay, let's do some demo
because I'm pretty sure it's going to
take some times and we can come back to
it uh
if uh if it's taking some time to just
build. So what I want to build is uh
three different apps. Uh agent flow
debugger. Okay, wait. Mhm. that
so yes I want to build three uh
different apps for to demo 4.8 eight uh
agent flow debugger uh pocket CAD which
build up uh a CAD application end to end
so it's like 3D u graphics you know when
you build a car like you can you have to
draw the piece of the car and a CAD
application is that uh it's basically
like yeah 3D uh generation of piece of
like whatever
um and FPS arena like it's it should be
like a first person shooter game. That's
uh
>> Oh, that's cool.
>> I'm going to put on a light because I
think my quality is really bad.
>> Let me check.
Uh
so, uh dark window closed path.
Okay.
And I'm going to go there.
So I'm going to create a new session
open folder
check.
Okay. Aon demo. No, I want to do the FPS
first. So I have the prompt ready. So
nothing have been set up. It's just
going to go like end uh from scratch.
Just going to take that the FPS arena.
Bam.
back
path. So, uh, build FPS arena end to end
a playable browser first person shooter
arena with react type create and vit
whatever whatever and 3GS 3GS pointer
blah blah blah.
>> Okay. What effort do you have enabled
right now
>> and we are going to do that with max. So
that should be ultra mode right?
>> Yeah. Well, I I never you I always do it
in terminal, but
>> instead of the prompt, if you do slash
effort, does it show you the to do the
selection as well?
Ah,
flash. No. Uh,
wait. Do I have the last update
path? No, because the effort is in the
trigger, right? Yes. So I don't have the
the is max ultra mode
ISF for means response but takes longer.
Okay, let me check if I should use the
the terminal instead. Uh cd
uh ship ship show.8
It's
uh brew upgrade
upgrading
>> because he even added effects to the
terminal.
>> If you go to Ultra Code, you get like a
>> Yeah. Like the I saw that on Twitter
like the Yeah.
>> the the purple radiant.
>> Yeah. You know, Theo said that it would
be um
Antropic is building fetus to make you
addicted to the
to the
>> It makes you think like Dragon Ball Z
like you have a Super Saiyan.
>> Yeah. Or more cas.
>> Yeah.
>> Removing. Okay. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Okay. Cool. So, uh
clothe.
Okay.
slash effort
path and we want okay so max was not
even
>> max was rainbow
>> and boom
nice
>> see and here it says it's x high plus
dynamic
>> yes
>> overflow orchestration
>> nice or
>> workflow orchestration
>> okay are you right ah okay so Maybe.
Wait, where am I? Why am Okay, I was
completely off green.
I don't need to zoom that much.
Okay, next. That's cute.
So,
do I have the prom still? I don't think
so. So, I'm going to take it again. Uh,
am I in
trouble the PWD?
Oh yeah. Opus 4.8. Oh no. Ah
>> try slashmodel and see what
>> in the the game stuff.
>> FPS FPS back
load. Okay.
Back. Am I? No. I'm in F. Let's go back
to Dragon Ball Z. Bam. Path
stack. Okay. So,
uh, Fob FPS arena blah blah blah. Okay.
So, let's see what it goes. Um,
>> and you also added on 4.8, right?
>> Uh,
yes.
Uh, you can't use ultra mode without
4.8, right? I don't know. I haven't
tried.
>> Let me see by.
>> Yeah. Recommended. Yes. Oh, 1 million
context, too. Ding.
Okay. I I should I should change that
because uh that's bad. Uh path. Okay.
I'm going to do
that because I can't see anything.
Uh replace
window.
Uh, clothed. We don't want clothes. We
want
Why is my ghost here? Okay. Nice.
Okay. Uh, nice, nice, perfect, perfect,
perfect.
Is that changing? Oh, it's not changing.
Okay, whatever. And then I want to
uh import the CAD app.
Pocket CAD. Boom.
And I didn't change the folder. So I'm
going to do that back. Uh
add
load
back.
So same thing.
That's the prompt. Oh, low effort. Ah
effort again. Back. Boom. Buff. Puff.
Yeah.
>> Uh, so what we want here it's uh
Okay, that's crazy. I resized it and
then I have that.
>> Yeah, it does something weird.
>> What the heck?
The was like screaming at
the terminal is right.
>> I can't I can't res What the heck?
>> Why is it zooming in?
Okay. So, uh, pocket card end to end a
Polish browser cut tool for designing
and simple laz cut bracket or enclosure
plate react typescript blah blah blah.
Jesus, that's a lot. Uh, what about the
FPS? Oh, what I write the source file.
Uh, oh, okay. I think I need to share
multiple uh
I'm going to share multiple screen
because Oh, I can't. No,
I can't. I need to replace it.
Uh, okay. Oh, replace. Wait. Uh, window
entire screen window
type.
Let me kick off npm install in the
background while I the source file.
Uh, so npmable. No browser installed
yet. What?
No browser. I have brave. What are you
talking about? Uh, okay. 3 minutes. Use,
by the way, to ask a quid. Yeah. Okay.
That before.
No. Let me relax.
Okay. No problem. Okay. So, it's
building and the cat. Okay. So, same
thing for the uh CAD app. It's um
it's building it's building it. And then
the last one, last example was the agent
orchestrator demo path load path.
And I want to replace
window.
Okay, we are back.
Uh effort
Dragon Ball Z.
>> Yes.
>> Do you like those animation in a cameo?
>> It is cool for the first time and the
second time, but
if it is after a week, I I want to be
able to just disable it.
>> Yeah.
>> But if you see it for the first time and
it's new, then it's cool.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's like, you know, the
features when they push like the pet
companion stuff. Mhm. Like I don't I
don't want that.
Why?
Okay. And this one will be uh agent flow
debugger end to end a polish visual
debugger for autonomous coding agent
runs blah blah blah. The app must
include full screen app UI with a graph
canva
simulator that move a task through the
workflow. So basically reprompt ship
code but ultra ultra mode. Mhm.
Cool.
>> Okay. So, all of the other files are
Yeah. writing npm apps. And in term of
usage, I was 100% this week. Uh where is
my Okay, here.
Oh, not okay. Um
I'm going to check my usage quickly.
>> I'm okay. Yeah, maybe it needs to finish
the prompt first or the entire uh
Oh my god. Okay. Um
I changed my email address to
uh like the domain to uh Google
Workspace and that's [__] up
everything.
All right. Why?
>> Because the synchroniz because I put the
the same address.
>> Yeah, it's creating icons now. Oh my
god. Um, okay. I should have changed
that before.
I'm going to change that to my other
computer.
Max
uh setting
usage.
I have already used 16% of the five
hours.
>> Yeah,
>> ultra effort is is really
>> ultra.
>> So, yeah, I I've set up like the Oh, I
didn't click this one. No, I did. Right.
>> And you're doing three projects at the
same time and it is doing a research for
each one.
>> Yeah.
So yeah, I I said I I I moved my Vincet
and Vincet ship shipdev to a workspace
account. It created a temporary email
for this uh personal uh Google email
>> and then created the same workspace one.
But no, when I use Google O for on the
apps, it doesn't match the Google ID,
but the email the the email uh match.
So, it create me another account.
>> Yes.
>> Uh okay. So, I'm curious about how long
it will take to generate all of the
but yeah. Okay. Nothing is uh
uh ready yet. Okay, cool. Uh path path
check close
>> because on my last feedback check it it
has been working for 21 minutes
but it was not on fast.
>> Oh I didn't put fast.
>> No.
>> Ah
>> I don't know if you can change that
>> if you just say stop go to fast and then
proceed
>> to go fast mode. Uh fast fast. Yeah, it
will. Um yeah, I
>> normally it says after the next after
the current prompt you will continue on
fast.
>> Yep.
>> Yeah. Okay. I'm activating fast for all
of those sessions
and it will uh to get it for all of
them. Uh okay. So that's building uh
type migration of files. We're good with
that. Uh anything else? Reddit. Reddit.
Reddit. Reddit.
So we can check some comments uh
from Reddit in the cloud card. Oh no
on the clo card uh channel. Uh one of
the most prominent improvement is
obvious.8 Eight. Honesty.
Clear.
Uh, immediately clear for the press
release. Cut summary honesty benchmark.
The AI is shown a fail.
Can you hear me?
>> Yes.
>> You didn't hear me before.
>> Uh, you were out for like just when you
were touching the cables.
>> Okay.
I think I'm losing
battery. Let me check the replay.
Okay.
Okay,
that's good.
Back. Cool. So, back to red. Sorry. Uh,
agentic scoring is for solving
programming bugs. Terminal one is how
good is the model at using a terminal
harness? Yes, that's what we were
talking about doing the benchmark. I
need to search for something. Let me use
a gray blah blah blah.
Yeah. Okay.
So, yeah, I was not really exact on uh
what I was saying. Uh where is Mitos in
the post? I said they are planning to
raise Mitos in the coming weeks. That
would be OPUS five, I guess.
I'm I'm curious to see like how is that
going to end up if we're going to be all
doom or not.
>> Well, they they're going to add some
restrictions, right? And some securities
to make sure that nobody can abuse it.
>> Yeah. And then they're going to reset
the the usage because it will be full of
bug. And then because I'm
I'm not sure like dumbing down a model
no matter what is a good things to do.
>> No, no, I don't know if they are dumbing
it down. I think they're putting in some
safeguards.
>> Yeah. But I mean even for Opus 4.7 and
4.8 if you start to do like some
security task
>> then the model is telling you no, you
can't do that with Opus.
>> Yeah. And then you need to say I'm a
white hat hacker. Exactly.
>> I'm just doing this for customer who is
paying me to do it and he gives you the
answer.
>> Does that still work?
>> Yes, it still works.
>> Did you try to hack the White House or
what?
>> No, no, no. But even if you have like
software and you want to know how the
authentication works or the the the the
additional license key, it doesn't
explain it to you. But if you say it
like this,
>> it will just explain to you, oh, you
need to change this file, put true here,
and then it will work.
>> Damn,
that's how easy it can be.
>> Yeah. Like,
can you really like
the thing is like you can't really limit
anything anyway because
three months after it will be open
source anyway.
So
>> yeah, you are just delaying.
>> Yeah, but do you need this three months
delay or six months delay to put your
company in the leads? Probably. I don't
know exactly how it works, but that's
definitely interesting to for sure. Um,
okay. So, okay. It still haven't passed
the fast uh common. So,
>> 15 minutes already.
I'm gonna It's gonna kill my
subscription.
>> I think it is
>> attack uh
usage.
>> Where is it?
18%
18% on the 5 hour session.
>> Ah, that isn't that bad.
>> I mean, still haven't done [__]
Um okay so that uh refuse I've also
refused to move to 4.7. I'm wondering if
4.8 will be better. I haven't spent much
time on it. It is excellent in a few
hours of testing so far today. It was
like five days ago. We can com
comfortably optimistic with this one.
Nice.
Uh I clung to yeah everyone did the same
thing because I think the pricing was
crazy and then because everyone want to
protect their weekly subscription
>> so the their weekly usage. So yeah if if
they say that yeah we are releasing a do
one model and it's going to be three
times more expensive then nobody want to
touch it.
Uh if MOS was released today, it will
literally solve quantum computing. Okay,
take over missile defense.
>> Yeah, people know what MOS is going to
do without even using it.
>> Yeah, but also like since they talk
about it like
internet is still here.
>> Yes.
>> So
I know
>> still didn't finish.
>> Yeah. But but I know some like North
Korean uh spy would have got it and then
destroyed the wall.
>> Yeah. Well, it still didn't happen. And
they actually gave companies access
already.
>> Yeah. But we do we know what they've
done with it.
>> Nope. The only thing they explained was
uh or that they publish is, hey, we
found so many zero day vulnerabilities
and that's it.
>> No explanation on what it is, how they
solved it.
>> Yeah. nothing that I found.
>> Yeah. So,
I I don't like I think it's good
marketing, but like that's going to beat
them in the ass
soon. Like you can't do that all the
time.
Dev Dev server live at local host. Let's
go.
>> Okay. Share it.
back
replace
window FPS arena.
Okay,
so move fire left click. Okay, all for
auto jump reload. Okay.
Oh,
but this is cool. You have actually a
working game already.
Jesus.
>> Oh, that was a bug. He walked right
through the pillar.
>> Yeah, there is no collision. Yes.
>> Yeah,
>> but maybe we can fix that. Score kills
enemies.
>> Yeah, it it counts at all.
>> That's crazy. That's kind of cool.
And see there is the lights effect. Oh
no. Okay. It's the when the when it
dies.
>> But this is like before people used to
code on something like juke nug or
whatever like quake.
>> Yeah.
>> Forever. And now you have it in a few
minutes.
>> And there is like a ammunition too. You
don't see it but I have the counter of
ammunition.
Like the ammo
I can reloading.
That's nuts.
Okay. 15 seconds. Okay. What? Okay. Game
over. I died.
>> Do you also have a scoreboard right now?
>> No.
>> Pause. There is a pose.
Elf. Okay. Wait. you don't see all of
the option. But if I do that,
um, wait, I can do that.
Look,
see, elf and ammunition.
And I can reload. And it's reloading.
Boom.
That's kind of sick, man.
Okay. So, this one is good.
Um,
like
uh Canva running the full verification
uh
like
replace
window. Bam.
Like
in 18 minutes, we have something that
works.
>> That's cool. And now it's just
optimizing.
>> Yeah.
>> Make this better. Make this better. Give
me an option to swap guns or whatever.
>> Add a reloading animation.
Oh, okay.
And the enemies are going through the
columns.
>> Mhm.
Uh so check for collision issues.
Okay.
>> And it would be cool to add a bigger
boss after 10 kills.
Check for collisions.
Add waves. And at the end of the third
waves, you add a boss.
Nice, nice, nice.
Okay,
cool. Time out. FPS verify. Verify
uh pointer locker error gun. Okay. Okay.
Uh scene is non blank. A truly blank
canva yellow. Okay, whatever. Uh, the
arena render beautifully floor grind and
with death glowing tire wall blah blah
blah. This is exactly right. The first
screen is the game and in game start
over with control click to play blah
blah blah.
>> So this is actually what they said that
Opus 4.8 would do. You give it a prompt
and it decides on each subtask.
>> Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah. Like the user
added new requirement made task. So it's
it was not even done. How my
verification baseline is green then
implement all of the new features.
>> It doesn't just before it would just
start coding or whatever you ask and now
I said no no no we can start. We need to
do some checks first make sure that all
works and then we can proceed.
>> I like that.
>> Yeah that that makes it look so much
better
and it's even managing. Yeah I I I saw
that before with like 4.7 but like yeah
nesting almost done thinking with XI
effort. So it during the task it's also
able to change the effort.
>> Yeah.
Okay. That's it.
Um for the CAD application I is still
building.
I didn't expect the CAD viewer 3D stuff
to be more complicated than a game. Uh
and same thing for the agent flow
builder.
Yeah, it's still building the UI after
60 minutes.
So, right now we have like yeah uh 47
minutes of like uh ultra mod.
It's kind of cool. I like that. That's a
good uh
>> So this now we are happy with Opus 4.8,
right? This is a good result.
>> I mean that's definitely impressive.
Uh, should we wait a bit again? I We
could build mobile games.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. This is something you
could play on mobile.
>> Okay. Do I have uh wave kills enemy?
Okay. I don't have the wave yet. Is
there a laz? Oh, no. It's the laz. It's
the shooting. But uh
>> what happens if you jump?
Oh, see everything they the AI thought
about everything.
>> Uh,
wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Uh, I would be curious if we can
add texture from GPT image
because we could create the sprites and
have uh, but they don't shoot at me too.
Like the enemies should have guns.
Well, that's for the next update.
>> Yeah, but first we build we build the
the skateboard and then we have a car,
right?
>> Mhm.
>> That's lit.
>> Yeah. You add two wings and the car
flies.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, path
t
uh path place FPS area arena. Bam. No,
not the one.
Replace.
Yes.
Waves. It's coming. It's coming. Total
waves. Bus active boss else.
Okay. Okay. Uh we can we can continue to
track that because I'm excited.
Uh attack. Okay. And the other app, not
the CSS. Okay.
No, the comprehensive [__] was a polish
leave. Okay, so the agent flow is
getting polished. I created a mission
control
>> and the pocket cat stuff it's coming
soon. Okay, so we have some notion of
the boss. Let's see what goes.
>> How many uh how big of is the usage
right now?
>> What?
>> We were at 18% usage. Oh yes.
>> Before this update,
>> uh 20 22%.
>> Mhm.
>> 5% weekly.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, that's definitely more expensive.
But uh I mean, is that better to spend
more tokens and have a longer workflow
or
smaller task, cheapest, but you have
more human in the loop? I think you need
both. Yeah, it depends on how much
influence you want to have. If you want
to have more influence yourself, you do
smaller tasks.
>> Yeah.
>> If you don't care and just want the
result, let it let it rip.
>> Yeah. But like for example Yeah. Like
exactly. But like for example, we can do
QA with like ultra mode blah blah blah.
>> Mhm.
>> And build apps with codeex.
>> Yeah,
that's what I'm doing.
>> That makes sense.
And then I also don't mind if it if it
burns a lot of tokens because I don't
use it for coding.
>> Yeah. H
>> So I have tokens to spend.
>> Ultra mode fast. Boom. Boom. Boom. Let's
go.
>> Yeah. Let's go fix it.
>> Uh do do you have time a bit?
>> Yeah, I have some time.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Uh because yeah, I'm
curious about this. Oh, play right. Play
what? Play. Okay. So the other one will
build pass for the CAD app. Can I
uh run dev?
Okay. So looks like this one will be
running
almost ready. Oh, let's see.
>> Okay. So generate motor. So,
oh, okay. Okay. So, it's loading.
That looks good.
Okay. Wait, what?
Okay. Going to raise you
hole.
Okay. So, it's a bit buggy
like for example.
>> Yeah. But it's just the first version.
>> Yeah. But I wanted to I asked if I can
load a model to
Okay. So, first generate laz cut
controller bracket. Did you ever use a
3D software like that?
No, not like this. I did use the What
did you use the 3JS?
>> Yeah, it's all 3GS, but you know, like
it's the for the for the people. Yeah.
>> Yeah. The only thing I did, but it was
over a year ago, I made a cube that you
can turn around in all the directions.
>> Mhm.
>> And it had um
all all sorts of materials in it. So,
you were able to turn it around and
watch materials from each side. And what
I did to make sure that it looked like a
real thing, a designer had the images
from each side created. So I pasted all
the images inside the cube on the
materials.
>> Mhm.
>> And that made it look like a real life
cube.
>> Okay.
>> But that was like
Opus 4.1. I don't know. It was a really
old version.
Oh,
>> you did that with Opus 4.1? Damn. Yeah,
but it didn't look as good as this.
>> I think if I can do it right now, it
would save me so much time.
>> Probably. Yeah. Uh,
okay. So, holes. Okay. But I don't
That's not what I wanted. I want drag to
orbit. Okay. Uh, extraction. Redo. Undo.
Okay. Reset. Okay. Nice. Laza cut
controller bracket. But I wanted to have
Okay. So CAD um stick
example
example.
Okay. So
if I give it that will it be enough?
I'm just trying to find
an image that we could use. Okay. So is
nice.
So if I give it that the goal would be
to reproduce this image.
>> So
copy image. I'm going to do build CAD
path. What?
Okay. I'm going to the it doesn't it
t
mechanical card uh
tech
path.
Can you replicate this image in the
project?
I'm going to share it. That's going to
be more clear place.
So, custo
uh I want to load a source image as a
card spec and then I want to be able to
edit the values of the spec directly in
the app.
Oh, puff. Okay.
>> How far is the game?
>> Uh,
no type check and build to catch any
errors. Okay, nice. Uh, it's coming.
It's coming.
>> Cool.
>> Replace.
Go. Bam. Bam.
Uh, it's building. It's building
everything. Checking if there is any
errors. Reload bar. Reload bar. banner.
That looks like Okay. Boss Boss bar
wraps.
If that works, that's going to be sick.
Um
Oh, look.
Bas research preview. High speed mode
for 4. Draw for usage credit at higher
rate. [__] off.
Ah, you can do it without paying
additional.
>> Oh god.
>> So that's how to make Well, what did we
say in the beginning?
>> Make them like an addict first and then
charge money.
>> It's crazy, bro. It's insane.
Local lost. Wait, what? What? What the
[__] is it? The port the port is not
correct.
Oh, ser.
Oh, okay.
uh is running detach responding. Okay.
So
that was the P of the software. Okay.
Okay. Aent flow debugger. So now
back back.
Okay. So what do we have here?
Okay. Okay. So that's a React flow map.
>> Mhm.
>> Pending Q plan build test pending. Okay.
>> Uh
>> that's a loop.
>> Yeah, but where are we?
Pending. Pending. Pending. Pending.
Everything is pending, bro.
Okay. So that's not working. Oh, aent
float debugger pocket build cap. Oh,
it's it's ideal. Okay. Is it still
building? Okay, wait. Because I don't
think it's
Oh, it killed the server. The
>> Ah, see you're doing three things on the
same server. That's
>> wave one.
>> Oh, you have the laser beam.
>> I think we had it before. And you have
your And ah now we can see your health
bar and your uh
>> Yes. But because I resized the wave.
>> Oh, that's cool.
>> Okay, wait. It Oh, there is animation.
Oh, there is
>> Yeah, for reloading.
>> Okay, wait. I want the collisions check
>> here. See, it walks around. It can't go
through anymore.
Okay. Okay. Okay. We have to.
That's so [__] cool.
>> Okay, we're almost at the bus.
>> Yes.
Yeah.
>> Two left, one left.
>> We We should have bonus and new weapons,
too,
bro. We are building a a game.
>> Oh, it's a bigger one.
>> Okay, just a bigger one. Yeah,
>> bro. That's sick.
>> Now, the question is, does it do more
damage as well?
>> Oh, yeah, it does.
That's so
>> Oh, you out of time.
>> No. No. Oh, did I? No.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No. Oh, it reset it because
you
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Bro,
I want to continue this game. This is
sick.
>> This is cool.
>> Okay. What? How much uh can we see
replace
tough?
So, okay. Fast mode. Fast mode is
bye-bye. Uh, cool. Puff. Fast mode.
Okay. Dynamic workflow.
Multi-dimensional address review app
completed. Three minutes. No, it didn't
take three minutes.
I think a bit more. Uh, tag tag npm
server. Okay, so that's cool. Okay, so
this app didn't really worked properly,
right? Wait, what is it doing?
>> Yeah, but I think we were also
using all the servers through each other
at the same time.
>> Yeah, that's that's probably an issue.
Yeah, like uh Yeah, like but see like
multiple agents running at the same
time. It kind of [__] up everything.
Bro, the review surface 20 confirmed
findings. It's reviewing it completed
the apps. Now it's reviewing it.
>> That's cool.
Okay.
>> How much uh uh usage do you have left?
>> Uh 20 28%.
>> 6% weekly.
>> Uh
>> so you can burn everything in an hour.
>> Yeah, that's the problem.
Uh okay. So
the flaky file the server is having the
update value. So the change is live yet
the boss still render brown. What
the pixel is identical to the crane. The
boss body. Okay. Okay. Uh okay. So, uh,
can
give me, uh, upgrades, new weapons that
I can, uh, drop that I can pick up after
I kill, uh, mob and make the, uh, mob
fire back.
Uh, upgrade. Oh, French accent.
Uh, upgrading. He did too much France
accent if I give it like a French
mustache.
>> Yeah.
>> Give me upgrades
for Nisses
new weapon
that I can pick up after I kill the mob
and make make the mobs
fire back
and add some skills
uh for the boss.
uh shield
uh uh faster
movement movement etc.
Buff
uh the boss no render has a clear maning
bright red giant with glowing eyes its
horn floating hells bar. Okay, so we
already had that.
>> Yeah, we already had that.
>> Test harness artifact. Prefill the
magazine. What? One check regressed. Oh,
bro. It's It's That's That's cool
because the full testing, the full
pipeline,
and it's been 40 minutes already. [__]
>> Mhm.
>> Okay.
>> Time goes fast when you're having fun.
>> Yeah.
Uh oh.
On the app, I think I'm going to cancel
and the other apps because I think we
saw the
>> Mhm.
>> we saw the demo, right? But okay, the
pocket cat build is complete and
verified. 1212 browser check pass
non non blank 3D another review is
running in the background and I will
fold any com fixes new request that
drawing is a flank pipe cross fitting
it's front view left alter blah blah
blah so analy good analysis of the image
I don't know if it's true but I will be
I will trust it um
how should the app turn a source image
into a editable spec pre extract this
drawing
I read this drawing no and ship it as
ready fully editable spec card. Yes, for
the demo it should be fine. Run blank
fat fit the tools. Okay, let's go.
Whatever. And for the agent
overflow stuff. I don't know what is
reading for the
for this app. Kind of weird. I didn't
really understand what it's uh
debugging.
>> It just started somewhere. What is
debugging itself? No, but like I want to
see the the flow of the agent, right, of
that uh but it was also connected to
pocket cat and I think it's uh it's
reloading pocket cat stuff inside the
agent flow. So I don't know I I we need
to reread the prompt.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh maybe you based both.
Uh, give me upgrade. Uh, T buff
puff buff puff. The user added another
feature request. Let me first lock in
the green baseline, finish the harness
fix, then implement a new features
applying the sample fix to the contact
damage check.
Uh, I kind of crazy.
How could we use that in our current
workflow?
>> Well, we are not game designers, right?
>> No, no, but okay. That that's a that's
right. But but bro, like uh we could
become
whatever we want
>> dev.
>> Yeah.
Well, how easy is it to create a
Minecraft game?
I mean a prompt that
>> I know Minecraft and Fortnite you can
earn money building the games and maybe
even in uh October uh GTA 6 is coming.
>> Oh yeah.
>> Yeah, that will be big.
>> I don't think you can vibe code GTA 6,
bro.
>> No, because people are making their own
maps in GTA 5.
Oh,
>> and they even had websites on the side
where you could buy stuff that you use
in the custom uh games.
>> Jesus.
>> But that is like I would like if I was
like rockstar, I would even like inter
uh integrate
um code or codeex or whatever
>> have those workflow just to for people
to build maps more easily.
>> Yeah. But I would say just make a a
horse event and have people do
competitions on unicorns and have them
drive.
>> Wow, that's sick.
>> And you can upgrade your unicorn by
paying us. Tada.
>> Pap health, ammo damage, pickup radius,
enemy range, blah blah blah. Boss shield
duration and rage.
Oh, you you make it bad.
Projectile damage, projectile speed,
barrage count, bar. What? Barrage
spread. What's barrage toast? Small
transient toast for pickup shotgun.
Let's go. Okay, we need to test that.
We're not We're not We're not
>> That's a finale.
>> That's exactly. Okay, I'm going to stop
the other apps because I want my weekly.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You want to make sure that
this can be finished?
>> Yeah. replace. Okay, that's kind of
interesting though because
confirm refuted. So it refused the
some binding and fixes.
It's it looks like ship code but
integrated to the CLI. Yeah, but don't
you think that eventually everything
that we build because we think we can
make it smarter and one or two versions
after it's integrated into cloud code
and codeex
>> but because yeah like those frontier uh
labs uh they can see what's um trending
on GitHub and what's useless and how
people what's useful and how people are
interacting with XY Z application and
say okay let's uh integrate
aka open claw to codeex uh agent
orchestration blah blah blah and then
boom you have that in the CLI
just imagine people relying on all this
and don't know how to do it themselves
anymore
>> I mean like I don't even remember how to
cut
you have to start again at hello world
>> yeah I ah I forgot but I mean we were
already doing it like react overflow uh
blah blah blah.
>> Yeah. How to how to uh do a CSS file
with Angular blah blah. Okay. How to
import properly my CSS file.
Uh that's nuts.
Okay. Uh looks like the
the third one no third one is over. Uh
okay. So
everything is green. Final end off aent
flow debugger down a full screen
operator gr visual debugger for
autonomous coding agent run build end to
end with react. Okay.
So that's not the same port. So that's
nice normal command. Bum bum bum. Okay.
Path. Oh, okay. It's not running. Um
Jack I started a dedicated port because
Okay. Uh
puff
run it again on path.
Uh okay. So four pen shell compact
toolbar graph canvas eight workflow
nodes start research plan build test
review done with fix below forming the
retry loop. Okay. Real simulator pure
deteristic state machine. Okay.
Whatever. Whatever. Uh, run control
start p inspector updates live. Final
report. Auto open after done. Cost 2.72
bucks. Team time 3 minutes 210 token.
One retry two fail checks. 90% average
confidence
20 artifact pre-stage blah blah blah.
Uh, that's interesting.
Uh process not after building I run a
multi adversarial code review enjoy.
Okay. The run is script deterministic by
design. The reviewer always fail once
then pass. Yeah. Review plan. Why? It
demonstrate the Oh, okay. Okay. It
demonstrate the retry path relability.
It doesn't call a real model. Cost time
tooken figures are simulated. Okay.
Uh reun. Okay.
Okay. So that's that's more demo than
job done.
>> Mhm.
But okay, so it looks like the same
pocket cat. Yeah, I think it loaded like
the previous.
Okay, so if I start play,
it's actually doing something.
>> I don't think so. I think it's a Yeah,
it's a simulation.
>> Ah, okay. But still, if this works, this
looks good. Uh, bro, that's uh that's
shape code.
>> Yeah. Yeah, but
>> I know. But that's that's okay that I
say looks good. Ship code looks good.
Okay, that's not exactly ship code, but
ship code is
it's uh it's lit.
Okay, let's do it again. Reset start.
So, you have the agent. Bam. Bam. Bam.
Oh no, that's
plan plan pass. Bum bum test fail. Okay.
Okay. So that's
that's lit.
>> Cool.
>> Okay.
>> No, let's see the end boss.
>> Yes.
Okay. So I'm going to kill that. I'm
going to push that to um background work
is running. Uh what what's running
one shell? Oh yeah. Okay, that's the
server. Okay, cool. Get it, bro. Get it.
Okay, so this one exit anyway. Bam.
Cool. Pocket CAD is still working on it.
And the boss the boss is still
uh the game is still building.
>> Ah, okay.
>> You need to go. Uh, I can spare a few
minutes.
>> Uh,
>> otherwise you're playing all by
yourself. That's no fun.
>> Okay.
Um, now it's time for the hood. The hood
jump. Which weapon?
Okay. Key frame. Bum bum bum. Yeah.
Uh,
are you going to try ultra ultra mod
again? Yes, I have to try it
>> 7%
on my weekly and current session 30 30%.
With three times but I mean for one
session
like if you do one ultra mode at a time
it's kind of legit man.
Okay.
Bam.
Okay, let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. We We have some other stuff to
do. Let's go.
Uh tag pocket cat still. Okay, so that's
scale. That's down. Okay.
>> Do you have the automatic continuation
on your API credits active if you 100%
usage?
>> Uh no, no, no. I deactivated that. I'm
not I'm not spending extra money. Yeah.
>> No, but my my settings it was toggled by
default and I didn't do it. So
>> really
>> I I checked it and I disabled it.
>> Yeah. No [__]
No, I'm not I'm not spending like 10 10k
months on AI.
>> Sure. Not.
>> Yeah. Especially for a demo for a stream
with like not a lot of viewers.
Uh tag tag. Okay. So that's done. We're
done with that. We done with that.
Uh path path. Okay, let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. We We have
We have other stuff. Okay. So, that I
don't need that. I don't need that. I
don't need that. Oh, I I closed too much
stuff. I don't have a brother open
anymore.
The problem. Uh now the property panel
shaper control react. Oh, no. That's
duplicated. Uh, insert the new features
check after contact damage test. Okay,
it's testing. So,
I think it will be live
>> in a few minutes.
>> Yeah.
Uh, local host
537.
Mouse click left.
Okay, wait. Uh, puff puff replace FPS
arena. Bam. I'm going to give you
the bar
of Okay. Uh, move. Look. Okay. Switch
weapon. Switch weapon. Okay. We have the
weapon. Mhm.
>> One, two, three, four. Okay.
So,
Okay. I don't have weapons.
Oh,
>> shotgun.
Okay.
>> And double damage.
>> Okay. Where is the rifle? Rifle.
Shotgun. Oh, it's a
>> Okay. That's cool.
>> Weapon. But
Oh, they fired. They fired back.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, and it Oh, you're
adding health.
>> Yeah.
You need to get closer for your shotgun.
>> SMG SMG SMG SMG SMG2.
>> Okay. It's It's change the colors of the
>> of the top of your gun.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> That's a cannon.
>> Cannon. Cannon.
I need
Okay. Okay. That's getting uh That's
getting crazy.
I should have had music. [__]
Oh, I don't like the cannon to Okay.
Health buff, rifle, SMG.
And see, like the damage is less.
>> Yeah. Yeah,
>> but it's faster. No, it's lit, bro.
Can we do that? Could we have done that
before? I have never tried it, but
I know that game studios doing this
setup, it takes them a few days to do it
properly.
>> I think.
>> Yeah.
>> Like with 3GS?
>> No, without AI.
>> Oh, yeah. No, I mean like Yeah, it it's
not uh it's not uh clear obscure
neither, right? Like,
>> okay, let's see how good the end is.
>> The boss. The boss. the boss.
>> Not the shotgun. That's too far away.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And it's managed
by that.
He has a
>> Oh, he has the shield
>> cannon. Oh, the cannon is lit.
>> More. Oh my god, that's lit. Okay, but
Oh, okay. So, the shield is if I'm too
close.
>> Yeah, the shield kicks in.
>> I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die.
Almost. Almost.
Okay, I can use that. Wait, I got it.
Yes,
>> that was cool.
>> That's
amazing. I had fun, bro.
>> I would say that was a successful test.
>> Yes, that was lit. Okay. 4 uh 4.8. Yeah,
4.8 is lit. Yes, we like it.
Um,
>> nice.
>> So, the question is, are you going to
create full-time Minecraft games?
>> I don't have time, man. I don't have
time.
>> But it could be a a real option.
>> Yeah. Like
because Yeah. If like a game is way
harder, games are games development is
way harder than any uh web pure web
stuff, right? But uh how can that act
into
like for example I have a github spec a
github issue spec can I use ultra mode
to just oneshot it?
>> I don't know but we can try this week
and let's
>> I'm gonna definitely do that
>> and I'm actually hoping that uh because
normally uh openai does an update a few
days after an comes. So, I'm actually
hoping that in the next week we get the
new 5.6.
>> Yes. And and I I hope it will not be
more expensive.
>> No.
>> But even if it's more expensive, that
that's great for entropic.
>> Yeah. But I don't want to uh more of my
subscription
>> and and and go like unemployed after two
days.
>> Nope.
So it's like working two days and having
28 days vacation.
>> Exactly. So that's a problem. But uh I'm
I'm amazed by this FPS game stuff. It's
a good benchmark.
>> Yeah.
>> Great.
>> Interesting. Okay, cool. Mitch, thank
you so much for your time.
>> Yeah, thank you for using your tokens
for us.
>> Yes, my pleasure.
Um I will post this uh the code um
to to the GitHub like the YouTube
channel uh repository.
>> Yeah, push the game as well so people
can modify it.
>> We could we could even like add more uh
oh we could work with it with codeex
>> and add multiplayers and stuff like
that. If we can use room and then a
score scoreboard blah blah blah that
would be sick.
>> That would be sick. Yeah.
>> Oh, okay. Okay. Okay. Uh let's talk
about it. Let's talk about it.
>> Yes.
>> Thank you so much for your time,
everyone. Uh thank you for watching the
video. Like, subscribe, and we will see
you next week.
>> Have a nice evening and nice day.
>> Bye.
>> Bye-bye.